

TRAN THIEN KHIEM

Address: Linh Trung District, Thu Duc, Ho Chi Minh City

Phone: +84 827 441 303

Email: khiemmm2004@gmail.com

Website:

SUMMARY

Dedicated tutor with experience teaching the full curriculum to elementary students and natural science to middle schoolers. I create engaging, supportive learning environments and offer personalized instruction online and offline. Available for 2-4 sessions per week, I aim to inspire a love for learning and help students achieve their academic goals.

WORK EXPERIENCE

Tutor Jan 2021 - Jan 2022

- Teaching 2 children in grades 6 and 8 in Natural Science subjects.
- Develop lesson plans tailored to the needs and goals of each student.
- Evaluate students' abilities and progress through tests and assignments.
- Foster a positive learning environment to motivate students to develop self-directed learning.
- · Assist in communicating with parents regarding student progress and any concerns.

Avhievements:

- Improved students from average to excellent.
- Enhanced student' critical thinking skills to increase overall subject average scores.

Teaching Assistant

Mar 2020 - Jan 2021

- Assisted and mentored students in groups and on individual basis.
- Supervised classes of 30-40 students during mealtimes, on the playground and on field trips.
- Support the use of technology in the classroom, including software and equipment.
- Assist in implementing strategies for students with special needs or learning disabilities.

EDUCATION

Software Engineering - University of Information Technology (UIT)

2022 - Present

- GPA: 3.5/4
- Inspiring Scholarship for excellent student 2022 2023

Mathematics Gifted Class - Bac Lieu High School for the Gifted

2019 - 2022

- GPA: 8.9/10
- National High School Exam (A00): 27 (Math 9, Physics 9, Chemistry 9)
- Competency Assessment Test (DGNL): 900+

SKILLS

- Teaching: Critical Thinking, Subject Knowledge, Assessment and Evaluation, Patience, ...
- Technical Skills: C++, C#, Javascripts,...
- · Languages: English
- Activities: Volunteer for the Mathlish Project, bringing knowledge to orphaned children at the shelter in Bac Lieu Province.